LILI COHEN

ENTRY-LEVEL COMPUTER PROGRAMMER

Meticulous Software Engineer offering wide-ranging expertise. In-depth understanding of web technologies with focus on delivering innovative business solutions. Excels in a fast-paced, high-energy and deadline-driven environment with willingness to take on additional tasks. Specializing in high-level programming language such as React, C#, C++ and JavaScript.

EXPERIENCE

Abc Inc., California — *Production Assistant*

NOV 2019 - FEB 2020

- Demonstrated self-reliance by meeting and exceeding workflow needs.
- Motivated and encouraged team members to communicate more openly and constructively with each other.

Amazon, California — Key Production Assistant

JUN 2019 - OCT 2019

- Liaised with various stakeholders, including producers and on-air talent to develop new program content and segments.
- Assessed deadline dates against production team activities and completed tasks within reasonable timeframes
- Remained alert, active and ready to respond to any request at any time using variety of available resources.

CBS, California — *Prize Fulfillment Page*

MAY 2016 - MAY 2018

- Worked with contestant prize-winners of the production by communicating the steps to receiving their prizes through legal documents and a presentation
- Audited team performance and compliance with contestants and industry standards.
- Maintained team efficiency by strategically delegating daily activities, monitoring output and rewarding positive contributions.
- Trained new employees in specific job requirements.

SKILLS

Expertise in Javascript, HTML, CSS, REACT, APIs

PHONE (818) 585-1230 EMAIL lili.cohen.tv@gmail.com

Project management

Working collaboratively

Reliable and trustworthy

Organizational skill

LINKS

GitHub

https://github.com/lilipcohen

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/lilicohen-78a93a1b3/

Portfolio:

https://lilipcohen.github.io/lili-co hen-portfolio/

EDUCATION

University of California, Los Angeles
August 2020-March 2021
Certification in Computer Programming

University of Colorado, Boulder
August 2014-May 2018
Bachelor of Science in Psychology